let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "About how many computer languages are in use?",
    answer: "2000",
    options: [
      "1000",
      "2000",
      "200",
      "500"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which company invented the floppy disk in 1971?",
    answer: "IBM",
    options: [
      "UNIVAC",
      "Atari",
      "IBM",
      "Microsoft"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who founded Apple Computer?",
    answer: "Steve Jobs",
    options: [
      "Bill Gates",
      "Sheryl Sandberg",
      "Sundar Pichai",
      "Steve Jobs"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is not a Linux distribution?",
    answer: "SO-2",
    options: [
      "Puppy",
      "Mint",
      "SO-2",
      "Debian"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which company was the first to introduce a handheld mobile phone",
    answer: "Motorola",
    options: [
      "Nokia",
      "Siemens",
      "Ericsson",
      "Motorola"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which inventor introduced the telephone, in 1876?",
    answer: "Graham Bell",
    options: [
      "Thomas Edison",
      "Graham Bell",
      "Michael Faraday",
      "James Watt"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The japanese electronics company Nintendo was founded in :",
    answer: "1889",
    options: [
      "1975",
      "1946",
      "1889",
      "1995"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Originally Amazon only sold which product?",
    answer: "Books",
    options: [
      "Books",
      "Toys",
      "Journals",
      "Video Games"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " What is the name of the British computer scientist who invented the World Wide Web in 1989?",
    answer: "Tim Berners-Lee",
    options: [
      "Tim Berners-Lee",
      "Barbara Liskov",
      "Alan Turing",
      "Ronald Rivest"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which prestigious university did Microsoft founder Bill Gates drop out of??",
    answer: "Harvard",
    options: [
      "Columbia",
      "Oxford",
      "Cambridge",
      "Harvard"
    ]
  },
  
];